LinkedIn.com/in/don-vo (651) 675-8655 DonOfTheDev@gmail.com

Don Vo

Professional Statement

A full-stack software engineer with over six years of industry experience specializing in web development, Agile methodology, quality assurance testing, and automated testing. Adept at collaborating with multiple teams, adapting to new technologies, and maintaining clean, readable code. Values code quality, automated testing, and application accessibility.

Experience

Software Engineer / Beech Valley Solutions, Atlanta, GA (Remote)

March 2022 - Present

- Implement front-end and back-end features for a staffing web application geared towards Certified Public Accountants, Auditors, Advisors, and more
 - Develop a new applicant system that allows internal users to view and manage potential consultants using React, TypeScript, CSS, GraphQL, Node.is, and PostgreSQL
 - Produce several Slack automations using TypeScript, Node.js and Slack API for user interactions in the application to provide internal users visibility on applicants and consultants
 - Create email automations for clients to provide updates on applicants they are interested in using TypeScript and Node.js
 - Modernize a Postgres-backed search to use ElasticSearch, greatly increasing performance while adding new capabilities such as full-text resume search
- Add custom continuous integration functionality to automatically mark stories as complete in our project management system as soon as they are deployed to production
- Collaborate with internal users to implement tools and features that improve their workflow
- Provide application support to internal users for application issues encountered
- Ensure high code quality by writing automated tests using Jest and participating in code reviews
- Gave product demos to the entire company to educate the team on new features

Software Engineer II / Infinite Campus, Blaine, MN

July 2020 - March 2022

- Implemented front-end and back-end features for multiple, diverse products designed for teachers and office administrators in K-12 school districts across the United States
 - Created features to simplify the user experience, such as managing field trips and after school activities, using HTML, Sass, TypeScript, Java and SQL
 - Produced back-end functionality to parse and convert curriculum from IMS Common Cartridge standards to be functional with existing features in the product using Java and SQL
 - Developed curriculum search features for teachers to find imported curriculum using HTML, Sass, TypeScript, and Java
- Wrote and maintain unit and API tests for codebase using Jest, Spock, and Cypress
- Managed and lead sprint planning

Software Engineer / Infinite Campus, Blaine, MN

August 2017 - June 2020

- Implemented front-end and back-end features for a web application designed for office administrators to run payrolls and manage time off requests
 - Completed web pages for creating and managing pay codes, deduction codes, pay periods, benefits, and for running payrolls using HTML, Sass, TypeScript, Java, and SQL
 - Created several report generators for time off requests, payment breakdowns, and amounts paid out per pay period using SSRS
- Collaborated with other teams to provide reusable components for consistency across the all products
- Wrote and maintain unit and API tests for codebase using Jest, Spock, and Protractor
- Managed and led sprint planning and retrospective

Software Engineer Intern / Infinite Campus, Blaine, MN

March 2017 - August 2017

- Implemented front-end features for a web application designed for office administrators to manage and store employee job information and associated documents
 - Developed a personnel report generator for a large teacher retirement system using SSRS
- Fixed bugs using a proprietary language based off of XSLT

Personal Projects

Pokémon Go Raid Bot github.com/rytrex/raidio

Designed and created a Discord bot for manually reporting upcoming and active raids in Pokémon Go as well as providing useful information to help players win the raid using TypeScript, Node.js, and Discord.js

Pomodoro for Habitica

github.com/rytrex/PomodoroForHabitica

Designed and developed a stand-alone web page that displayed a pomodoro timer which automatically updates a Habitica habit at the end of the timer using Angular and Habitica's API

Skills

Languages: TypeScript, Javascript, SQL, Java, GraphQL, HTML5, CSS, Sass, Python, Terraform, Groovy, C, XSLT

Frameworks: React, Angular, Protractor, Cypress, Hibernate, Jersey, Objection

Libraries: Kendo UI for Angular, Tailwind, React Table, Material UI

Technical: Git, Agile Scrum, Kanban, ElasticSearch, Node js, Continuous Integration, Continuous Deployment,

Kubernetes, Docker

Education

Bachelor of Science, Computer Science and Mathematics

Augsburg College, Minneapolis, MN September 2013 – April 2017

• National Honor Society: Pi Mu Epsilon